camh.ca 2011-11-30

# Privacy & confidentiality policy-CAMH

| 

You are here: [Home]()

CAMH places a high value on privacy, both in person and online.   Please visit CAMH’s privacy pages to learn more about our commitment to protecting the personal information of our patients and clients.  These pages contain information about our Privacy Office, our Privacy Notice, and our Privacy Policy.

The Centre for Addiction and Mental Health ("we",  "us" or "CAMH") is committed to maintaining the privacy of all individuals who use [www.camh.net](http://www.camh.net/) ("the Site"). 

This Site may contain links to other web sites. Upon entering other sites, you are subject to the privacy and security policies of those sites. This policy identifies the privacy practices of the CAMH Site only. 

No personal information (which means personally-identifiable information including, without limitation, your name, street address, telephone number, screen name and e-mail address) about the user is collected from users of this Site unless specifically and clearly requested, and only when the user provides it voluntarily. This Site does not use or collect digital cookies to track visitors. 

Personal information that has been provided by users is secure information and is requested to enhance the user's access to information at CAMH. We only use personal information provided for the express purpose for which it was collected unless the user specifically agrees to the use of the personal information for additional purposes. In order to prevent unauthorized access and ensure proper use of your personal information, we have developed electronic and managerial procedures to secure information provided on-line. In addition, personal information will not be shared with any third party. 

CAMH gathers general trend data concerning traffic on the website for statistical analysis. We also anonymously capture information about how users interact with our site and what pages they visit. This information is used for auditing and tracking purposes and to improve the content of the Site. The data we collect is used both collectively and individually for website research to create a better experience for the users of this site. This information is not linked with any individual or IP address. 

As a user of this Site who has provided personal information to CAMH, you can have access to your personal information for the purposes of correcting or updating any of your personal information or to delete the personal information you provided on this Site from our records.  A contact email address for such purposes will be provided at the points of collection of personal information on this Site. 

|
